{
    "subject": "resource/Roy_Webb",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Roy Webb",
    "human_readable": "The name of Roy Webb is Roy Webb.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9837942719459534,
            "question": "Is Roy Webb's name Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9717394709587097,
            "question": "Who is named Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9715740084648132,
            "question": "What is the name of Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9559499621391296,
            "question": "What is the full name of Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9324309825897217,
            "question": "Is 'Roy Webb' a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9279876947402954,
            "question": "Does the name Roy Webb identify a person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8035671710968018,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7472401857376099,
            "question": "What do we know about Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6718310117721558,
            "question": "How would you describe Roy Webb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6011682152748108,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything about Roy Webb?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Roy Webb is Roy Webb.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5056_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Roy Webb?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5056_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What do we know about Roy Webb?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5056_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Roy Webb?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5056_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5056_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The first document mentions \"Roy Webb\" as a person, and subsequent documents confirm that this is indeed the name of the American film music composer being discussed."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is based on the information provided that mentions \"Roy Webb\" multiple times, confirming his identity without contradiction."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}